Hey,
where's that other punk?
Huh?
Is that little asshole bringing the cops?
You dumb little high school bitch,
I got ya.
Hey,
- load faster.
- That's heavy.
You got the paperwork?
Yeah,
- I brought everything.
- Then hurry up.
Hey, hey, hey. Hurry it up.
Oh shit.
Hurry up!
Shit, shit.
- Hey, hurry!
- Hurry up!
Come on!
Come on, come on, come
on, come on, come on.
Let's get outta here!
KIM GIL-SU
- Hey hyung, sorry my battery was dead.
- Don't fucking bullshit me.
Tell me where you are?!
Hey,
it's over,
so you better come to Mangwoo-dong
with Yeong-i, that fucking bitch.
Seong-chan is here.
You better fucking hurry
or else I'm gonna sell him somewhere.
Got it?
Yes.
Seong-chan?
What'd he say?
I need to get going.
You stay here.
Rent out a room for a few days.
Where are you going?
Don't follow me.
Oppa!
ASSHOLE
What happened?
What's going on?
I'm at the address you gave me,
but no one's here.
Those shitheads
took Su-ho, didn't they?
Send me a friend request on WithMap,
like right now.
What?
You don't have it?
WithMap's on the app store. Download it.
It's a location-sharing app,
so get it and follow me.
Where are you going?
I don't know yet.
Make sure you bring the police.
Or we're really gonna die.
Okay.
Oppa!
I'm not letting you go alone.
I'm coming with you.
I'll be fine. Okay?
Bye.
Why did you send Su-ho there alone?
What are you going to do if
something happens to him?
YEONG-I:
COME TO MANGU-DONG FIRST
YOUR FRIENDS ARE THERE
WEAK HERO:
CLASS 1
You're so annoying.
How long are you gonna follow me?
Hey, knock it off.
Su-ho-ya.
You alright?
Hey how'd you uh-
how did you end up here?
I thought that you might be in trouble.
I was kinda worried.
I went to that guy's house
to give him the money,
but then they took me here.
Oh.
Hey, that warms me up like dogani tang.
- Wow.
- Hey, hey.
- I could go for a drink.
- Hey assholes, shut your
fucking mouths, alright?
Hey,
let us talk over here.
I'm sad enough as it is,
being tied up like this.
Also, smoking's
really bad for your health.
You keep talking.
Aw, shit.
Yeong-a.
Yeah?
Remember to stay quiet.
Don't act up.
You always say the same thing.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault we got involved
with Gil-su to begin with.
This wouldn't have happened
if you hadn't followed me.
Hey.
Do you like me?
Don't be an idiot.
Hello?
I just made a report about Mangwoo-dong.
Are you on your way?
Come here.
Hey, Seok-dae-ya.
Did I-
do something to hurt your feelings?
I fed you, and housed you.
I mean,
I even paid you a lot of money.
Why?
Did your heart get soft because
you got a family of your own?
I'll take the beating, hyung.
Nn, nn, nn.
I was just curious.
Get it over with.
Alright.
Take the beating then, asshole.
You piece of shit. Huh? Fuck.
You shithead mother fucker!
Oppa!
- Oppa, please don't.
- You bitch! So you --
You did it.
You're responsible for this.
Hey,
take this bitch, get rid of her.
Get off!
Let go, you fucking assholes!
Let go! Let go of me!
Get your grubby-ass hands off me!
Hey, Seong-chan-a.
You're turning fourteen this year, right?
Yes.
So you stabbed those guys then, alright?
Don't be such a coward.
You're a minor.
You won't get thrown in jail.
Agh,
I'm anxious.
JUNGNANG-GU
YEONG-I
Which one of you should I stab?
Eenie, meenie,
mi-
nie,
moe.
Ding, dong, ding,
dong.
Hey, man.
Let's work something out.
Shut your mouth.
Yeah? This might sting a little.
Okay?
God --
- Agh.
- Enough is enough, goddamn piece of shit.
Woah, woah.
Oppa!
Everybody stay still, or I will kill you.
Let's go, one on one, you and me.
- If I win, you leave us alone.
- Fucking shit.
What, you take me for a punk-ass bitch?
You asshole. Fuck you.
Fucking bitch.
Hey! Let go of me you fucking shithead!
Come here. Fuck.
God damn, asshole!
- I gave you food
- Fucker!
And a place to stay
right?!
Agh!
Damn it.
Stop before you really get
your ass beat to hell.
God damn.
Hey, Seok-dae-ya.
Are you at least having fun?
Huh?
You know that you'll never beat me.
Because
your big dumbass heart gets in the way,
you piece of shit-
Ow, fuck.
- Stupid bitch.
- You hit him from behind?
Enough is enough, you goddamn fuckers!
- You fucking bitch, I'll--
- You want to fuck around and find out?
Get Seok-dae oppa.
Hey, don't move.
- Fucking bitch.
- Hey, stay where you are, asshole!
- Not again.
- Agh, one sec.
Hold on.
Agh.
I'm bleeding. Just a minute.
Goddamn bitch.
You fucking bitch.
Die, you little shit.
Ever since Seok-dae fucking met you-
Die.
Shit, damn it.
- Oh no.
- Hyung!
Hyung!
Fuck,
I thought you were a dumbass kid.
But you're freakin' brave,
aren't you?
It's over.
The police are here.
They'll probably search
your car down there.
God damn it.
- Oh shit.
- Let's go.
Are you okay?
Si-eun-a.
What's going on?
I'm sorry I'm late.
- We almost died, can you untie us?
- Yeah.
Agh, ow my arms.
Let's get out of here.
Nice.
I'm never coming back
to an amusement park.
- Hey, why are they back?
- For fuck's sake.
Hey.
You think that you're so smart, don't ya.
These little fucking kids
trying to trick me?
Fuck.
I'm done playing your game.
- Go get them!
- Aw man, you should've told us.
Kick their ass!
Here we go.
Yeong-a.
Let's go.
We have to go.
Huh?!
The police.
- What?
- What are you doing?
- You gotta leave, now.
- Why?
Kids!
You little--
Come here!
- You psycho son of a bitch.
- You stupid fucking asshole.
- Move aside.
- Fuck.
Did you think I wouldn't stab you
just because you were a kid?
Huh?
That's why
you should've given me the money when
I asked for it, you little shit.
Yeah?
Huh?
Don't move!
Hands up!
Number two-twenty, this is forty-three.
All suspects in report two nine one
seven are involved in an assault case…
- You fucking little prick.
- Next time, you're all dead.
- Number two-twenty, this is forty-three.
- Stay where you are.
All suspects in report- Don't move!
I think there's some
kind of a misunderstanding-
These are live bullets.
Oh, we're cooperating, sir.
- Right?
- Uh-huh.
Wait,
didn't we play soccer together last month…
Agh.
Nobody move.
Hey, hey, hey.
I'm not.
Stay still.
Hey. Hey!
Yeon Si-eun!
Where are you going?
Shit.
You scared me.
Oh, fuck this.
This is some fucking bullshit, man.
I hate this.
Hey,
why're you fucking following me around?!
Huh?
Geez, this stupid little kid.
You're fucking impossible,
you little prick.
Fuck.
Where should I stab you?
Huh?
Hey!
Ah,
guess I gotta
kick your ass.
Why've you both been coming
after me all day?!
Shit man, I am so
sick of this crap.
Well?
Come on.
Shit.
- You're pretty good, kid.
- Yeah, and you're slow.
Hmm?
Shit head!
Hey!
That's it?
Oh, man.
Eat shit!
Hey,
have you lost your mind or what?
Why would you go by yourself
Huh?
You came.
Wow, what a load of shit.
You know,
you really are a psycho.
Yeah?
I'm not the only one.
You won't let me have the last word,
will you?
If I were you,
I'd let me win.
You psycho.
- Come here.
- Damn it.
What are you doing? Stop messing around!
Go.
- You must go.
- Stop this bullshit and come with us!
Fucking listen to me, Yeong-a!
Go.
It's not your fault.
You're really…
Let's go, nuna.
Hey.
- Come on!
- Hey! Fuck this, hey!
You're so annoying!
Hey, Jeon Seok-dae!
- I can't believe you!
- Young man,
put your hands up.
I said, hands up.
Let me fucking go!
- I already told you everything, fuck!
- Let go! Let go!
- Why won't you just let me go?!
- Shut up and cooperate.
- Get your hands off me, I'm cooperating!
- How humiliating, shit.
Come on!
Additional officers are on their way.
Stop resisting.
I'm not!
I'm coming for ya,
when I'm out, kay?
Yeah?
- Damn it! -Fuck!
- What's going on?
- Agghh.
- Let's not cross paths
anymore, you fucking dick.
Shit.
Ahh, dogani-tang.
Ahh, I'm so hungry, seriously.
Dogani-tang. Ah.
Do you have a tapeworm or something?
The moment I thought about dogani-tang,
I just couldn't get it out of my mind.
- With kkakdugi, aw man.
- Here you guys are.
What?
What a relief, you're still alive.
I thought this guy was dead.
Well, after you two left,
I went looking for Si-eun's
phone and stuff,
but I couldn't see anything,
so I took a while.
Here.
The screen's a little broken.
Thanks.
Uh, Yeon Si-eun-gun?
We need you to come to the
station to make a statement.
Your friend too.
- Uncuff me!
- You need to calm the fuck
- down, just have a seat first.
- You have no right to arrest me!
- I'm not fucking saying anything!
- Sit down, alright?
I'm sorry.
What?
You were right.
Because of me, Su-ho…
Sorry.
Don't
say that.
You were
late because I took the taxi alone.
I'm sorry too.
The superintendent and I made a deal.
It will be… our little secret.
You both are completely
irrelevant to this case.
What?
Si-eun-gun, your family doesn't need
to be made aware of this.
You should go home.
Excuse me.
The only person who did anything wrong
was the man named Kim Gil-su.
He blackmailed and exploited everybody.
I'd appreciate it
if you showed them mercy.
Okay.
Go on home.
Did you keep it
a secret from my father?
No.
We should head out too.
I mean,
I asked you to keep it a secret from him.
Let's go.
Is that so?
I'm telling you.
I heard you.
- You have to understand.
- That's why I'm listening.
Hey, psycho.
Let's grab a bite to eat, sometime.
Why do you all love food so much?
What's up?
How's Seok-dae oppa?
He's being questioned, inside.
He'll be fine.
What about the others?
I can't reach anyone.
The youngest one went home.
And you?
Hey.
What the hell?
Huh?
The assemblyman wanted you to give
that man an eye for an eye.
Sorry?
This is the police station.
- You're beating someone here?
- Go ahead.
I-I'm alright.
Bullshit fucking idiots. Fuck this.
Hey.
Stay still. Don't move a muscle.
Now, watch what I do.
One, two.
Okay? One, two.
That hurts.
Use your imagination,
like you're hitting a punching bag.
Okay. Hit me.
Dumb fuck. Hey, Maltese.
Come at me like your friends did.
Ahh.
Wait, never mind.
You're just their minion.
You're not their friend.
You're some kind of little fucking
coward compared to those guys-
All right, you fucking asshole.
Hey,
hit me.
Do it!
Come hit me!
Hmm?
Well…
She wanted to apologize.
Hello.
Wait.
You don't seem like someone
who's here to apologize.
My bad.
You're nuts.
How did it go with you?
I don't know if it's a good thing,
but Beom-seok's family's covering it up.
They took our names out of the case.
And Kim Gil-su's detained.
Is
Beom-seok's dad
a chairman of some place?
His family's secretary or whoever,
came by and said they'd pay
my whole hospital bill.
I declined,
but should I have just accepted it?
He's an assemblyman.
Oh Jin-won.
Wow.
How long will you be in here?
I'll be discharged tomorrow.
It's a light fracture.
Then like, can I sleep here tonight?
Yeah, do what you want.
All right!
Hey, you were freaking cool back there.
- Yeah, I'm pretty cool.
- Yeah, I got goosebumps.
"You wanna fuck around and find out?!"
"Enough's enough, you goddamn fuckers!"
Why are you copying me,
idiot? Did you fall in love?
Enough's enough.
Too bad, so sad. I'm Si-eun's.
Are you two dating?
That's not happening.
That's not happening?
We know where each other's
at at all times.
That's just
that app's main function.
You should just date each
other, you'd make a cute couple.
Enough's enough.
You little shit.
Huh?
What?
- What's this?
You were craving it.
Ugh, I'll gain weight eating this late.
Huh?
Wow, look how late it is.
You are so inconsiderate.
I guess,
I should eat some just to be nice.
Wow it looks amazing.
What is this feeling?
I just got the chills.
What's with you?
- What do you mean?
- I mean,
you.
You're being
way too sweet.
Huh?
Your eyes,
the way you act, talk,
and your face.
It's making me cringe.
Eat your food.
Si-eun you need to eat something too.
Are you a mindreader?
Well, before I'm an assemblyman,
I'm also a citizen and a father,
and am naturally, extremely interested
in the youth policies, obviously.
What?
Why did I
ever bring you here?
You are…
just the wrong kind of breed.
You know that?
ALL NAMES, PLACES, AND EVENTS SHOWN
ARE FICTIONAL
ANY SIMILARITY TO REALITY IS COINCIDENTAL